Guide to the Cornell Alumni Association records,1932-2013.
Cornell Alumni Association records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Alumni Association records, 1932-2013.
41-6-1058
Cornell Alumni Federation.; Cornell Alumni Association.
17.6 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Financial Records, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, membership records, minutes, scholarship information, reports, plans, dues and financial information, and other records of various Cornell Clubs (Women's and Men's). Also, invitations, programs, videotapes, and DVDs from the Frank H.T. Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Awards (FHTR), 2001-2011. Also large felt banner with Cornell Alumni Federation name and logo used at board meetings and at the Rhodes Award Dinner.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Formerly Federation of Cornell Clubs.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, membership records, minutes, scholarship information, reports, plans, dues and financial information, and other records of various Cornell Clubs (Women's and Men's).
Also, invitations, programs, videotapes, and DVDs from the Frank H.T. Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Awards (FHTR), 2001-2011. Also large felt banner with Cornell Alumni Federation name and logo used at board meetings and at the Rhodes Award Dinner.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Alumni Association.; Cornell Alumni Federation.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Federation of Cornell Clubs: Executive Committees, Various Records, and Correspondence
Series II. Board of Trustees and Federation Board of Directors Minutes, Mailings, Memos
Series III. Committees
Series IV. Scholarships, Awards, and the Federation Scholarship Awards Committee
Series V. Additional Uncategorized Alumni Association Records and Information
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Federation of Cornell Clubs: Executive Committees, Various Records, and Correspondence
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Questionnaires and Newsletter Mailing List (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Accommodations for Annual Meeting, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Questionnaires, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Treasurer's Report, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Treasurer's Report, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Questionnaires, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Cornell Clubs- Annual Meeting, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Treasurer's Report, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Newsletter, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Questionnaires, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Questionnaires, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Treasurer's Report, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Michigan Weekend Information, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee Meeting (New York), December 7, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Federation of Men's Cornell Clubs, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Proposed Resolution on Alumni and Public Relations (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Report (Misc.), June 21, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee Meeting, March 8, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Meeting of Presidents, October 13, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Treasurer's Report, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting Reservations, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting, October 18, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee Meeting, March 28, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Meeting, October 19, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- First Annual Dinner, October 19, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting, November 10, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Votes on Resolution (designed to improve University's alumni and public relations), July 1946 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Miscellaneous Minutes, Correspondence, and Information (Box 2)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs, President William F. Stuckle (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Federation of Cornell Clubs- Lists of area entering students (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Newsletter, Fall 1959 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Newsletter, 1950- Spring 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Participating Contribution, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Participating Contribution, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Bronze Plaque (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting, October 1956 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting, October 22, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting, November 1958 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Alumni Organization Procedure, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting, October 22, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Treasurer's Report, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Treasurer's Report, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Questionnaires, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Treasurer's Report, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting, October 9, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Applications for Annual Meeting, October 9, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Meeting Minutes, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Correspondence, 1944-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Officer Information from Chapters (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Membership Lists from Chapters (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Dues, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Rosters (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. II (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Fundraisers, Seminars, Misc. information for members (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Blinn, A.; Bullard, H.; Hill, May; Arnold, Mrs. J. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Secretary, Meeting Minutes (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Secretary, Meeting Minutes (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Executive Committee Meeting Minutes (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Executive Committee Meeting Minutes (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Regan, M. (Vice Chair of Secondary Schools Committee) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Zimmer, Mrs. J.H. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Justin, N.R. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Mackie, Mrs. Thos. T. (Treasurer) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Knauss, Mrs. E.S. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Morris, Mrs. T.A. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Rice, M.A. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Mackie, Mrs. Thos. T. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Vincent, E.L. (Dean) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Zimmer, O.S. (Cornell University Council) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Stilwell, Mrs. A.O. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Rogers, Mrs. Wm. P. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Rose, M.E. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- White, G.L. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Malott, D.W. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- O'Sullivan, Mrs. M. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Club Manual Material, 1959 to Completion, 1959, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- General Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- General Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Annual Meeting, October 18-19, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- General Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- General Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Club Manual Material, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Rogers, William; Newspaper Articles Relating to Dinner by Cornell Club of Washington D.C., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Rogers, William; Correspondence Relating to Dinner by Cornell Club of Washington D.C., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Club of Washington Papers, November 1957-February 1958 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- General Correspondence, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- General Correspondence, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Dues, Bills, etc., 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarships, Dues, Acknowledgements, Misc., 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. Information, 1933-1947 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Correspondence re: Dues, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Annual Meetings, 1925-1953 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Misc. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Timetable, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Annual Midwinter Meeting (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Federation of Cornell Clubs- Cornell Club of State College (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Members of Kappa Delta Epsilon (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Dues, Bills, etc. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Benefit (in Ithaca) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Constitutions (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Dues, Bills, etc., 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 27`)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Biographical Records (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Officers and Directors (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Bequests (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Cornell Club of Ann Arbor (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- President's Letters (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Endowment Fund Correspondence, January 1939-March 1940, January 1939-March 1940 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Awards Committee Minutes and Related Papers, April 1961-1962, April 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Awards Committee, June 9, 1962, June 9, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Awards, 1962-1963, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Applicants, 1962, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Questionnaire, October 1963, October 1963 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Handbook, 1960s, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Correspondence, February 1961-April 1961, February 1961-April 1961 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Awards Committee, Minutes of the Meetings and Correspondence, April 1960-September 1961, April 1960-September 1961 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Feedback for Scholarships, Spring 1964, Spring 1964 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Women's Clubs- Guidelines and Logistics, 1950-1960, 1950-1960 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Versions of the Cornell Woman's Clubs' Official Handbook, 1960s, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Feedback from Cornell Woman's Club Scholarship Participants, February 1964-May 1964, February 1964-May 1964 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (with May K. Hoyt), 1962-1963, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Roster of Cornell Clubs (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Biographical Records of Cornell Club Rostered members (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Treasurer's Records (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Membership (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Treasurer's Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Placement Service (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Miscellaneous Information (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Conference (Fields of Work for Women), 1935-39 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Membership, 1936-1939 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. News Clippings (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. News Articles (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Various Misc. Records (Box 12)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Various Misc. Records (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Cornell Clubs- Executive Committee and General Mailings, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Federation of Cornell Clubs- Executive Committee and General Mailings, 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Federation of Cornell Clubs- Constitution; Executive Committee Meeting Minutes (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee Mailings; Various Awards, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Federation of Cornell Clubs- Meeting Minutes; Executive Board and Speaker Listings (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs - Officers' Handbook, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Endowment Fund, 1940-1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Roster (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Constitution, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- History, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Memos, 1939-1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. on Fields of Work for Women, 1934-1941 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Suggestions for Speakers/Forum Programs, etc., 1935-1942 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Speakers at 1942 Forum, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Conference: War Jobs With a Future, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Conference: Fields of Work for Women, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. on Fields of Work for Women, 1942-1946 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Misc. on Fields of Work for Women, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Tea Parties, 1940-1942 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Women's Club of New York, 1914-1938 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Women's Club (of New York)- Various Records, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Women's Club (of New York)- Various Records, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Women's Club (of New York)- Various Records, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Women's Club (of New York)- Various Records, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Women's Club (of New York)- Various Records, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Women's Club (of New York) - 2nd Sch., 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Membership Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Executive Committee Mailings, 1979-1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Mailings, 1985-1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - General Mailings, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - General Mailings, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - General Mailings, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - General Mailings, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - General Mailings, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Federation Mailings, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Federation Mailings, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Federation Mailings, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Federation Mailings, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Federation Mailings; Board Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Federation Mailings; Board Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Federation Mailings; Board Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1920-1926 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1998 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Organizational Charts, 1970-1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's and Men's Clubs- Merger, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Club Presidents, 1979-1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, Mailings, Memos, Correspondence, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, Mailings, Memos, Correspondence, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, Mailings, Memos, January - April 2008 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, Mailings, Memos, Correspondence, May - December 2008 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Federation Board of Directors Lists, 1979-2001 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Federation Board of Directors Lists, 2002-2011 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Series II. Board of Trustees and Federation Board of Directors Minutes, Mailings, Memos
  - Board of Trustees Ballot/Voting Information, 1970-79 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Cornell Clubs Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, 1979-1983 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, 1984-1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, 1990-1997 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 10-11)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 19-20)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, January-April 2008 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, May - December 2008 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, 2009-2010 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, July 2008-June 2009 (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, July 2009-June 2010 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors- Meeting Minutes, Mailings, Memos, July 2009-June 2010 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Series III. Committees
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Public Relations Committee (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Strengthening Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee, May 20, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Executive Committee (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs- Applications for Annual Meeting, October 9, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 24)